{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Network \u0026 Router Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/39784/":{"taskOID":39784,"originalTaskOID":39784,"setID":316,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":502507,"questionDisplayText":"Type of network","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of network do you want set up?","shortQuestionText":"What type of network do you want set up?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7031,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wireless","answerDisplayText":"Wireless","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203348,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wired / Hardline","answerDisplayText":"Wired / Hardline","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4960,"questionDisplayText":"Items Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select which devices will be part of your home network. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1547,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Computer","answerDisplayText":"Computer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Printer","answerDisplayText":"Printer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2404,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fax","answerDisplayText":"Fax","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2345,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"External storage devices","answerDisplayText":"External storage devices","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3104,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hub (for multiple data connections)","answerDisplayText":"Hub (for multiple data connections)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3884,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Modem","answerDisplayText":"Modem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5581,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Server","answerDisplayText":"Server","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203349,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Tablet","answerDisplayText":"Tablet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200420,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Scanner","answerDisplayText":"Scanner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203350,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Smart phone","answerDisplayText":"Smart phone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4962,"questionDisplayText":"Dedicated Server","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will you have a dedicated server?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":40001,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Homeowner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will you provide materials for this request?","shortQuestionText":"Homeowner to provide materials?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":502507,"questionDisplayText":"Type of network","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of network do you want set up?","shortQuestionText":"What type of network do you want set up?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7031,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wireless","answerDisplayText":"Wireless","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203348,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wired / Hardline","answerDisplayText":"Wired / Hardline","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7031,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wireless","answerDisplayText":"Wireless","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203348,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wired / Hardline","answerDisplayText":"Wired / Hardline","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4960,"questionDisplayText":"Items Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select which devices will be part of your home network. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1547,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Computer","answerDisplayText":"Computer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Printer","answerDisplayText":"Printer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2404,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fax","answerDisplayText":"Fax","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2345,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"External storage devices","answerDisplayText":"External storage devices","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3104,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hub (for multiple data connections)","answerDisplayText":"Hub (for multiple data connections)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3884,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Modem","answerDisplayText":"Modem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5581,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Server","answerDisplayText":"Server","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203349,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Tablet","answerDisplayText":"Tablet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200420,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Scanner","answerDisplayText":"Scanner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203350,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Smart phone","answerDisplayText":"Smart phone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1547,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Computer","answerDisplayText":"Computer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Printer","answerDisplayText":"Printer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2404,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fax","answerDisplayText":"Fax","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2345,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"External storage devices","answerDisplayText":"External storage devices","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3104,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hub (for multiple data connections)","answerDisplayText":"Hub (for multiple data connections)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3884,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Modem","answerDisplayText":"Modem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5581,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Server","answerDisplayText":"Server","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203349,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Tablet","answerDisplayText":"Tablet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200420,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Scanner","answerDisplayText":"Scanner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203350,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Smart phone","answerDisplayText":"Smart phone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4962,"questionDisplayText":"Dedicated Server","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will you have a dedicated server?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":40001,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Homeowner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will you provide materials for this request?","shortQuestionText":"Homeowner to provide materials?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/39784/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":39784,"taskName":"Computer Network or Wiring - Install or Repair","taskDescription":"Install, Upgrade or Repair Computer Network or Wiring","xmTaskDescriptor":"Network \u0026 Router Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":45,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"computer network equipment wiring","textMessagingName":"Computer Network","rolloverLongDesc":"Refers to stranded pair wires that look like phone wires but are larger \u0026 utilize larger modular jacks.  Typically used to connect networked computers \u0026 related equipment.  Can be surface mounted or run inside walls.","rolloverShortDesc":"Larger phone wires \u0026 jacks for computer networks.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install, Upgrade or Repair Computer Network or Wiring.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Router Repair \u0026 Setup \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Computer Network \u0026 Wireless Router Setup","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":25,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Computer Network Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Computer Network or Wiring - Install or Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Computer Network \u0026 Wiring Project","urlName":"Computer-Network-or-Wiring-Install-or-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Router Repair \u0026 Setup Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Computer Networks, Wireless Setup","searchKeywords":"computer,network,equipment,wiring","emcCategoryOid":-12006,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":316,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}